Guide to the Thomas E. Dixon Papers, 1967-1993
Duke University. University Archives
Thomas E. Dixon papers 1967-1993
Duke University. University Archives
Dixon, Thomas E. (Thomas Edward), 1948-
18 linear feet Extent: 18,000 Items
Thomas E. Dixon was a Duke University administrator from the 1970s through the early 1990s, holding the positions of Associate University Controller, Controller and Co-director of Human Resources, Associate Vice President for Administrative Services, and Vice President for Administrative Services (1989-1993). The Thomas E. Dixon Papers, 1967-1993, contain correspondence, memoranda, reports, meeting agendas and minutes, and other materials that document Thomas Dixon's tenure as Vice President for Administrative Services and other positions he held at Duke University from the late 1970s through the early 1990s. Records mainly consist of subject files pertaining to operations of non-academic divisions of the university, including Auxiliary Services, the Facilities Management Department, the Office of Human Resources, and the Telecommunications Division (Tel-Com). Also represented are committees with which Dixon was involved, including the President's Advisory Committee on Resources, the Safety Task Force, and the Committee on Social Implications of Duke's Investment Policy. Other materials include minutes of several committees of the Duke University Board of Trustees and a variety of reports, plans, and blueprints about the construction and opening of the Washington Duke Inn & Golf Club in 1980s.
UA.10.03.0006
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the University Archives to use this collection.
Records of the University's Board of Trustees which have been in existence for at least fifty years are available for scholarly research with the permission of the University Archivist. Access to records which have been in existence for less than fifty years shall be granted only by special permission, in writing, from the Board of Trustees.
For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist.
Provenance
The Thomas E. Dixon Papers were received by the University Archives as a transfer in 1994.
Biographical Note
Thomas E. Dixon (Ed. D., Duke University, 1980), held various administrative positions at Duke University from the 1970s through the early 1990s, including Associate University Controller, Controller and Co-director of Human Resources, Associate Vice President for Administrative Services, and Vice President for Administrative Services (1989-1993).
Collection Overview
The Thomas E. Dixon Papers, 1967-1993, comprise correspondence, memoranda, reports, meeting agendas and minutes, and other materials that document Thomas Dixon's tenure as Vice President for Administrative Services and other positions he held at Duke University from the late 1970s through the early 1990s. Records primarily consist of subject files pertaining to operations of non-academic divisions of the university, including Auxiliary Services, the Facilities Management Department, the Office of Human Resources, and the Telecommunications Division (Tel-Com). Several committees on which Dixon served or interacted with are represented, including the President's Advisory Committee on Resources, the Safety Task Force, and the Committee on Social Implications of Duke's Investment Policy, the last-named of which, among other issues, investigated corporate divestiture in South Africa in the late 1970s and early 1980s. Other prominent groups of materials in the collection include minutes of several committees of the Duke University Board of Trustees (see Restrictions) and a variety of correspondence, meetings, and reports that document the planning and building of the Washington Duke Inn & Golf Club, opened in 1988. Numerous blueprints appear in the Washington Duke folder group, as well as in other subject files in the collection.
Arranged as received, with the exception that all Board of Trustees files have been transferred to Box 1.
Subject Headings
Dixon, Thomas E. (Thomas Edward), 1948-; Duke University. Auxiliary Services; Duke University. Board of Trustees; Duke University. Committee on Social Implications of Duke's Investment Policy; Duke University. Facilities Management Dept; Duke University. Office of Human Resources; Duke University. President's Advisory Committee on Resources; Duke University. Safety Task Force. Reports -- 1993; Duke University. Telecommunications Division (Tel-Com); Duke University. Vice President for Administrative Services; Washington Duke Inn & Golf Club (Durham, N.C.) -- History; Corporate divestiture -- South Africa; Blueprints
Detailed Description of Collection
- Accession A94-31, 1967-1993, (19 boxes)
  Correspondence, memoranda, reports, and other materials documenting Thomas Dixon's responsibilities as the Vice President for Administrative Services as well as other positions he held in the university. Mainly composed of subject files pertaining to operations of non-academic divisions, including Auxiliary Services, Human Resources, the Telecommunications Department (Tel-Com), Facilities Planning and Management, and Duke University Food Services. Minutes and memoranda from the Operating Boards of various divisions are included as well as minutes of the Management Board. Also contains minutes of various Board of Trustees meetings--see Restrictions.
  - Board of Trustees, 1985-1988, (23 folders) (Box 1)
    [RESTRICTED: Records of the University's Board of Trustees which have been in existence for at least fifty years are available for scholarly research with the permission of the University Archivist. Access to records which have been in existence for less than fifty years shall be granted only by special permission, in writing, from the Board of Trustees.]
    - Board meeting, 1988 Sept. (Box 1)
    - Board meeting, 1989 Feb. 24-25 (Box 1)
    - Executive Committee, 1988 Apr.1-Nov. 4, (4 folders) (Box 1)
    - Board meetings, 1988 Feb. 26-Dec. 10, (3 folders) (Box 1)
    - Board meetings, 1987 Feb. 27-Dec. 12, (4 folders) (Box 1)
    - Executive Committee, 1987 June 12-Nov. 6, (3 folders) (Box 1)
    - Board meetings, 1986 Feb. 28-Dec. 12, (4 folders) (Box 1)
    - Board meetings, 1985 Sept. 27, Dec. 6, (3 folders) (Box 1)
  - President's Suggestion Box, 1987-1989, (4 folders) (Box 1A)
    [Restricted until 2014.]
  - United Way, 1987-1988, (3 folders) (Box 1A)
    [Restricted until 2013.]
  - LAN (Local Area Network) Report Problems, 1985, (3 folders) (Box 2)
  - Tel-Com memoranda, 1987-1989, (3 folders) (Box 2)
  - Tel-Com switch--T. Dixon info, 1986-1988, (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Agendas--ESM (Expanded Staff Meeting), 1986-1990, (2 folders) (Box 2)
    [Restricted until 2015.]
  - Dober and Associates, 1986-1987, (3 folders) (Box 2)
  - DUFS (Duke University Food Services), 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - DUFS (Duke University Food Services), 1987-1988, (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Washington Duke Inn & Golf Club, 1981-1991, (23 folders) (Box 2)
    [Restricted until 2016.]
    - Washington Duke Inn and Golf Club, 1990-1991 (Box 2)
    - Hotel, 1981-1986, (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - 751 intersection, 1987-1989, (2 folders) (Box 2)
      Contains blueprints.
    - The Continental Companies, 1987-1989 (Box 2)
    - Adornato, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Comments, 1989-1990 (Box 2)
    - Electric and salvage, 1987-1988 (Box 2)
    - Expenses, 1988-1990 (Box 3)
    - Minutes/articles, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
    - Signage, 1988 (Box 3)
    - Structural problems, 1988 (Box 3)
    - Tel-Com, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
    - Trees, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
    - Water and sewer, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
    - Golf course hotel, 1987-1988, (2 folders) (Box 3)
    - Ground lease, 1987, (2 folders) (Box 3)
    - Metric [Contractors] progress reports, 1987-1988, (3 folders) (Box 3)
  - Marriott Food Services evaluation and DUFS, 1987-1988, (5 folders) (Box 3)
  - Sports Festival, 1986-1988, (Folder 1-6 of 8) (Box 3)
  - Sports Festival, 1986-1988, (Folder 7-8 of 8) (Box 4)
  - Agreement(s) by and between Duke University and North Carolina Amateur Sports, 1986-1988, (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Job Enhancement Program, 1984-1986 (Box 4)
  - "What's important"--memorandum, 1985 (Box 4)
  - TED (Thomas E. Dixon) chronological files, 1982 Jan.-1986 June, (11 folders) (Box 4)
  - Facilities Planning and Management and Physical Plant staff meetings, 1987-1988, (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Physical Plant/Facility Planning Annual Report, 1986-1987 (Box 4)
  - Material Support Department Annual Report, 1986-1987 (Box 4)
  - Employee Occupational Health Service Annual Report, 1986-1987 (Box 4)
  - Communications Department Annual Report, 1987 Sept. 30 (Box 4)
  - Administrative Services Division FY 86/87 Actual vs. Budget Growth Analysis and Work Load Indicators, 1986-1987 (Box 4)
  - Auxiliary Services, 1987 (Box 4)
  - Department of Facility Planning Annual Report, 1985-1986 (Box 4)
  - Physical Plant 1985/86 Annual Report, 1985-1986 (Box 4)
  - Office of the Associate Vice President and Business Manager, 1984/85 Annual Report, 1984-1985 (Box 5)
  - Auxiliaries 88/89 (#3), 1988-1989, (3 folders) (Box 5)
  - Facilities Planning and Management--staff meeting minutes, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Facilities Planning and Management--FY 88-89, 1988-1989, (3 folders) (Box 5)
  - Housing, 1986-1989 June, (3 folders) (Box 5)
  - Human Resources Monthly Reports, 87/88 and 88/89, 1987-1989, (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - HR 88/89, 1988-1989, (3 folders) (Box 5)
  - Material Support, 86/86, 87/88, 88/89, 1986-1989, (4 folders) (Box 5)
  - Campus safety reports and files, 1989-1992, (25 folders) (Box 5)
    [Restricted until 2017.]
    - Complaints/articles, 1989-1990, (3 folders) (Box 5)
    - Cameras, 1989-1990 (Box 6)
    - Campus security--memos/letters, 1989-1990 (Box 6)
    - Dorm access, 1989-1990 (Box 6)
    - Dorms/Admin. bldgs. Devices, 1989-1990 (Box 6)
    - Escort/Deans/Network, 1989-1990 (Box 6)
    - Federal legislation, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Forums, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Funding/costs, 1989-1990 (Box 6)
    - Hot Line responses, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Lights requests, 1989-1991, (2 folders) (Box 6)
    - Other security concerns, 1989-1992 (Box 6)
    - Phones/emergency phones, 1989-1990 (Box 6)
    - Publications, 1989-1990 (Box 6)
    - Responses to TED dept. memo, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 6)
    - Weekly light tour, 1991-1992 (Box 6)
    - Routes survey, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Security devices, 1989-1990 (Box 6)
    - Self-defense, 1989-1992 (Box 6)
    - Student demands/responses, 1989-1990 (Box 6)
    - Van/rape crisis, 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Hewitt Study (on Duke benefits), 1985-1988 (Box 6)
  - DUFS (88/89), 1988-1990 (Box 6)
  - YMCA, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Skarulis Reorganization, 1984 and undated (Box 6)
  - Johnson & Higgins--Analysis of Health Plan Utilization, 1985 Jan. 1-1987 (Box 6)
  - American Recording Orchestra at Duke, undated (Box 6)
  - Amaker, Tommy, 1987 (Box 6)
  - Administrative Services Conference, 1986-1987, (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - Expanded Staff Meetings, 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - Budget cuts, 1987 (Box 6)
  - Operating boards, 1986-1990, (12 folders) (Box 6)
    - Cost operations, 1986-1988 (Box 6)
    - Food service, 1986-1989 (Box 6)
    - Tel-Com, 1987-1989 (Box 6)
    - Housing, 1986-1989 (Box 6)
    - Human Resources--Employment, 1987-1990 (Box 7)
    - Human Resources, 1987-1989 (Box 7)
    - Material Services, 1987-1990 (Box 7)
    - Office Services, 1986-1990 (Box 7)
    - Public Safety, 1986-1989 (Box 7)
    - Retail Stores, 1986-1989 (Box 7)
    - Special Events and Conference Services, 1986-1989 (Box 7)
    - Treasury, 1986-1988 (Box 7)
  - Housing, 1990-1991 (Box 7)
  - PCB Removal, 1986-1990 (Box 7)
  - Kahr/Huber, 1989 (Box 7)
  - Kuhn, Mrs. Fred, 1976-1989 (Box 7)
  - McDonald Reserve Funds, 1986 (Box 7)
  - Meningitis, 1987 (Box 7)
  - Jackson, Jesse, 1988 (Box 7)
  - Health plan monitoring, 1986-1990, (4 folders) (Box 7)
  - High school (Durham County), 1987 (Box 7)
  - Duke Association for Troop Support, undated (Box 7)
  - Desert Storm, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Chrysler, 1989-1990 (Box 7)
  - Breakfast Club, 1990-1991 (Box 7)
  - Blacknall Memorial Presbyterian Church, 1986 (Box 7)
  - Infrastructure Fund, 1987-1991, (6 folders) (Box 7)
  - PACOR (President's Advisory Committee on Resources)--six meetings, 1992 Jan. 15-Mar. 4, (6 folders) (Box 7)
  - [Operating] Board evaluation1988 (Box 7)
  - Operating boards, 1985-1990, (Folder 1 of 3) (Box 7)
  - Operating boards, 1985-1990, (Folder 2-3 of 3) (Box 8)
  - TAC (Tel-Com Advisory Committee) minutes, 1989-1991, (3 folders) (Box 8)
  - Tel-Com Advisory Committee, 1990, (4 folders) (Box 8)
  - Tel-Com Advisory Board, 1989, (6 folders) (Box 8)
  - Management Board--eight meetings, 1988 Jan. 21-Nov. 22, (Folder 1-6 of 8) (Box 8)
  - Management Board--eight meetings, 1988 Jan. 21-Nov. 22, (Folder 7-8 of 8) (Box 9)
  - Management Board--five meetings, 1987Jan. 29-Oct. 2, (5 folders) (Box 9)
  - Business and Finance Advisory Committee, 1975-1983, (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - Homesites, 1986-1988, (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - Urban Land Institute, 1986-1988, (3 folders) (Box 9)
  - UW/AHA (United Way/American Heart Association), 1988-1990, (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - Rauch Award, 1986-1990 (Box 9)
  - Fire Station Proposal, City of Durham, 1984-1989 (Box 9)
    Correspondence and memoranda on location of proposed fire station in relation to the Duke Primate Center. Contains blueprints.
  - Measles, 1989 (Box 9)
  - Adult Ronald McDonald House, 1984-1987 (Box 9)
  - A. Pat Brown Scholarship, 1967-1987, (3 folders) (Box 9)
  - Property Management, 1979-1981, (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - Property Administrators, Society for, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Huestis, C.B., 1983 (Box 9)
  - Plant Accounting, 1978-1981 (Box 9)
  - Student loans--Zero Base Budget, 1982 (Box 9)
  - ZBB (Zero Base Budget), 1979-1983, (3 folders) (Box 9)
  - OMB A-110 Pilot Study, 1982-1984 (Box 10)
  - Committee on Social Implications of Duke's Investment Policy, 1976-1985, (3 folders) (Box 10)
    Meetings, notes, and research of committee charged with investigating Duke's investment portfolio with regard to various social and political issues, including the university's relationship with companies with holdings in nuclear power, advertising aimed at children, and the countries Argentina, Chile, and, especially, South Africa. The work of this committee appears to precede the later Committee on Social Implications of Duke Stock--see also the Inventory of the South Africa Policy Implementation Committee.
  - Broad Street, 1986 (Box 10)
  - Tel-Com Renovations, 1989-1992 (Box 10)
  - Primate Center, 1989-1990, (3 folders) (Box 10)
  - Campus Planning Study, 1987, (2 folders) (Box 10)
  - Earl Walls Associates, undated (Box 10)
  - Cassidy and Associates, Inc., 1988-1989 (Box 10)
  - Technology Center, 1987-1988, (4 folders) (Box 10)
  - Visiting Committee, 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box 10)
  - Childcare, 1987-1990, (Folder 1-2 of 3) (Box 10)
  - Childcare, 1987-1990, (Folder 3 of 3) (Box 11)
  - Other than SRI projects, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Science Resource Initiative (SRI), 1988-1990, (23 folders) (Box 11)
    - Space/cost, 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Campaign, 1988 (Box 11)
    - Dept. Programming, 1988-1989 (Box 11)
    - Architects, 1988-1989 (Box 11)
    - Herb [Schuette]1988-1989 (Box 11)
    - Science Resource Initiative, Duke University, 1988 Apr. (Box 11)
    - Agenda/minutes, [SRI Steering Committee]1989 (Box 11)
    - New committee, 1989 Oct. 16 (Box 11)
    - SRI Misc., 1989, (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Finance, 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Academic Space Inventory File, 1989 (Box 11)
    - Board of Trustees, 1988 (Box 1)
    - SRI Budget, 1989 (Box 11)
    - SRI, 1988-1989 (Box 11)
    - Faculty Advisory Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 11)
    - Steering Committee, 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - SRI Misc., 1989-1990, (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - SRI, 1989 (Box 11)
  - Auxiliaries, 1987-1988, (Folder 1 of 6) (Box 11)
  - Auxiliaries, 1987-1988, (Folder 2-6 of 6) (Box 12)
  - Tom Dixon (including copies of Board of Trustees minutes), 1987 (Box 1)
  - Public Safety 88/89, 1988 (Box 12)
  - Safety--prior enhancements, 1989 (Box 12)
  - Public Safety Budget 87/88, 1987 (Box 12)
  - Public Safety 1986-88/89, 1986-1989, (3 folders) (Box 12)
  - Directions for Progress: A Report to the Duke University Board of Trustees, 1980 Sept. 26 (Box 12)
  - Physical Plant Department Customer Service Handbook, 1979 (Box 12)
  - Zero Base Budget of Grounds Maintenance, 1980-81, 1980 May 2 (Box 12)
  - Zero-Base Budget: Office of Budgets and Measurements, FY 1982-83, 1981 Sept. (Box 12)
  - Zero Base Budget of Special Services, 1981 Feb. 4 (Box 12)
  - Zero Base Budget of Office Products, 1980 Apr. 9 (Box 12)
  - "Zero-Base Budgeting of Accounts Payable, 1981-82, "1980 Dec. 19 (Box 12)
  - Duke University Public Safety Department, Police Operations Manual, 1990 (Box 12)
  - Servicemaster, 1986-1989, (6 folders) (Box 12)
  - Auxiliary Services 85/86 -- 86/87, 1986-1987, (2 folders) (Box 12)
  - Facilities Planning and Management (7/86 -- 6/87), 1986-1987, (Folder 1 of 3) (Box 12)
  - Facilities Planning and Management (7/86 -- 6/87), 1986-1987, (Folder 2-3 of 3) (Box 13)
  - Human Resources 86/87, 1986-1987, (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - HR--87/88, 1987-1988 (Box 13)
  - 1985-86 Annual Report Preparation, 1986 (Box 13)
  - Annual Report, 1985-1986, (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - Trackmobile, 1988-1989 (Box 13)
  - Dorm window safety, 1986 (Box 13)
  - Dorm damages--ad hoc committee, 1985-1988, (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - Communications Department Annual Report, 1985-19861986 Sept. 1 (Box 13)
  - Tel-Com Proposed Budget Summary for Fiscal 1986/87, 1986 (Box 13)
  - Auxiliary Services, 1983-1986 (Box 13)
  - Auxiliaries 88/89, 1988-1989 (Box 13)
  - Cheerleader Camp, 1987-1988 (Box 13)
  - Business manager, 1984-1987 (Box 13)
  - Alumni House addition, 1986 (Box 13)
  - Alumni lounge, 1988 (Box 13)
  - Annual Report, 1986-871987-1989 (Box 13)
  - Baxter Health Care, 1989-1990 (Box 13)
  - Beaufort Conference, 1987 (Box 13)
  - Duke Gardens 87/88 Budget, 1987 (Box 13)
  - Budget Proposal FY 87/88, Auxiliary Services Administrative Office, 1987-1988 (Box 13)
  - Auxiliary Services' Key Information to Their FY 87/88 Product/Service Program, 1987 (Box 13)
  - Auxiliary Services' Key Information to Their FY 87/88 Product/Service Program, 1987 (Box 13)
    Note: not identical to the above.
  - Auxiliaries 87/88 budget, 1987 (Box 13)
  - General, 1986-1987 (Box 13)
  - Public Safety 89/90, 1989-1990 (Box 13)
  - Princeton Review, 1987 (Box 13)
  - Pizza RFP (Request for Proposal), 1988-1990 (Box 13)
  - Helicopter display, 1987 (Box 13)
  - CUPA (College and University Personnel Association), 1986-1989 (Box 13)
  - American Dance Festival Agreements, 1986-1989, (3 folders) (Box 14)
  - Riverbend Properties, 1988 (Box 14)
  - Scerbo, Barry, 1990 (Box 14)
  - Semans, Tommy, 1989 (Box 14)
  - Senior Class Gift, 1988 (Box 14)
  - Sod Farm Study, 1988 (Box 14)
  - X-ray equipment, 1985 (Box 14)
  - Naslund, Robert, 1989 (Box 14)
  - Racquet Club, 1984-1986, (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Auxiliaries, 1989/90, 1988-1990, (3 folders) (Box 14)
  - Facilities Planning and Management 89/90, 1989-1990, (3 folders) (Box 14)
  - Human Resources 89/90, 1989-1990, (3 folders) (Box 14)
  - Material Support (89/90), 1989-1990 (Box 14)
  - Tel-Com, 1988-1990, (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - WDI--Pro Shop Construction Reports, 1988-1990 (Box 14)
  - Washington Duke Inn (9/87-5/90), 1987-1990, (3 folders) (Box 14)
  - Racquetball Facility, 1986-1987 (Box 15)
  - Knott & Roberts1988 (Box 15)
  - Newsstands, 1988 (Box 15)
  - Building projects, 1985-1986 (Box 15)
  - Auxiliary Information Systems Controls Review, 1988 July 22 (Box 15)
  - Joe Pietrantoni -- finance, 1988-1990 (Box 15)
  - Burlington Industries Property, 1987 (Box 15)
  - Crapo, 1988 (Box 15)
  - Fees, 1987 (Box 15)
  - Food poisoning, 1987 (Box 15)
  - Hanes House/NROTC, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Housekeeping, 1987-1990, (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - Housing 90/91, 1990-1991 (Box 15)
  - Housing 89/90,1989 (Box 15)
  - Invoices, 1986-1987 (Box 15)
  - President's Advisory Committee on Resources (PACOR), 1987-1992, (48 folders) (Box 15)
    - PACOR, 1987-1990, (3 folders) (Box 15)
    - Resources Committee, 1989-1990, (3 folders) (Box 15)
    - Resources Committee/SRI, 1989 (Box 15)
    - Facilities Planning and Management report, 1989 (Box 15)
    - Administrative Services, 1989 (Box 15)
    - Auxiliaries, 1989-1990 (Box 15)
    - Tel-Com, 1989-1990 (Box 15)
    - Extraordinary 1990/91, 1989 (Box 15)
    - HR--Charges [Changes?], 1989 (Box 15)
    - Public Safety, 1989 (Box 15)
    - MS [Material Support], 1989 (Box 15)
    - Agendas and minutes (meetings), 1991 Sept. 11-Nov. 27, (10 folders) (Box 15)
    - Fall meetings, 1991, 1991-1992 (Box 15)
    - Report to PACOR: University Financial Aid Programs Prepared by Office of the Provost, 1991 Apr. 10 (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous, 1990-1991 (Box 15)
    - Agendas and minutes, 1991 Jan. 8-Mar. 12, (Folder 1-3 of 5) (Box 15)
    - Agendas and minutes, 1991 Jan. 8-Mar. 12, (Folder 4-5 of 5) (Box 16)
    - Agendas and minutes, 1990 Sept. 18-Dec. 17, (6 folders) (Box 16)
    - PACOR, 1990 (Box 16)
    - PACOR--Formula, 1990 (Box 16)
    - Academic Administration, 1990 (Box 16)
    - Reports to PACOR--Auxiliary Services, 1989 (Box 16)
    - Reports to PACOR--Communications Division, 1989 (Box 16)
    - Reports to PACOR--Facilities Planning and Management, 1989 (Box 16)
    - Reports to PACOR--Human Resources, 1989 (Box 16)
    - Reports to PACOR--Material Support, 1989 (Box 16)
    - Reports to PACOR--Public Safety, 1989 (Box 16)
  - Budget files--various departments, 1985-1988, (20 folders) (Box 16)
    - General, 87/88, 1987 (Box 16)
    - Cost distribution, 1987 (Box 16)
    - Facility Planning Department, 1987 (Box 16)
    - Material Support--87/88 Budget, 1987 (Box 16)
    - Human Resources, 1987 (Box 16)
    - Material Support, 1987 (Box 16)
    - Office Services Division, Communications Department: Proposed Budget Fiscal Year 1987/88, 1987 Mar. (Box 16)
    - Overhead Codes; Director; Planning; Administrative Maintenance; Work Order Payroll, 1985-1987 (Box 16)
    - High Voltage; Heating Plant; Energy Management, 1987 (Box 16)
    - Grounds; Sanitation; Housekeeping, 1987 (Box 16)
    - University Buildings; Utilities Maintenance, 1987 (Box 16)
    - Physical Plant Department Budget Request Summary FY 87/88, 1987 (Box 16)
    - Budgets (various departments), 1987-1988, (7 folders) (Box 16)
  - Board of Trustees meetings, 1989 May 12-Dec. 9, (4 folders) (Box 1)
  - University Architect, 1986-1991 (Box 17)
  - Dronsfield, 1991 (Box 17)
  - Parking and parking lots, 1986-1989, (6 folders) (Box 17)
  - Parking Task Force and Report, 1988-1989, (6 folders) (Box 17)
  - Research Triangle Institute, 1978-1981 (Box 17)
  - Research Triangle, Committee on, 1981-1982 (Box 17)
  - Gothic Book Store, 1986-1987 (Box 17)
  - Lobby Shop/Gothic Book Store, 1987-1989 (Box 17)
  - HR Monthly Reports, 89/90 and 90/91, 1989-1990, (2 folders) (Box 17)
  - Droege Computing, 1989 (Box 17)
  - Divestment (South Africa), 1987 (Box 17)
  - Blue Cross/Blue Shield Audit Report, 1984-1989 (Box 17)
  - Betterments, 1987-1988 (Box 18)
  - Auxiliaries Capital, 1990 (Box 18)